# **Dylan Armstrong**

Orlando, FL | (407) 230-1632 | <u>Dylan.Craig.Armstrong@gmail.com</u>

Linked In: https://www.linkedin.com/in/Dylan-Armstrong

Github: https://github.com/DoleTM | Portfolio: https://doletm.github.io/Portfolio/

#### **SUMMARY**

Web Developer specializing in creative front-end web pages and fluid back-end functionality. Experience in IT working with hands on equipment and using back end ticketing programs to resolve issues. Ability to create platforms practical for the end user through UI/UX elements and connecting data. Strong communication skills with a demonstrated history of leading without authority.

#### **TECHNICAL SKILLS**

Node.js | MySQL/Postgres | Javascript | JSON | API | JQuery | MongoDB | React | CSS/SASS | HTML | FTP | PHP | Angular | Version Control/Git | MVC | Bootstrap | OOP | Ember.js | Heroku | Materialize | Command Line

#### **PROJECTS**

Safely: A website that uses geolocation or zip code that determines if they are safe based on a crime data API.

- Responsible for connecting and displaying the data from Firebase to the front end webpage.
- Voted first place in functionality, creativity and presentation out of 12 different projects.
- This project utilizes Tailwind, Javascript/JQuery, Orlando City Crime API, Firebase and CanvasJS.

Deployed site: https://soc33.github.io/Safely/ | GitHub Repo: https://github.com/soc33/Safely

**Furiends:** Social media platform designed for the user to post pictures of their pets.

- Responsible for back end functionality and contributing to the front end User Interface.
- ☐ After making an account the user is able to upload and comment on photos.
- ☐ This project utilizes Bootstrap, EJS, Cloudinary, Passport.js, Bcrypt.js, DataURI, MySQL/Sequelize, MVC. Deployed site: <a href="https://agile-gorge-44903.herokuapp.com/">https://agile-gorge-44903.herokuapp.com/</a> | GitHub Repo: <a href="https://github.com/gutierrez88/Furiends">https://github.com/gutierrez88/Furiends</a>
- **Web-Scrape:** Webpage that scrapes articles from the web and saves favorites/comments in a database.
  - □ Sole contributor from concept to production.
  - ☐ Utilizes the CRUD functions for comments on blog posts.
- ☐ This project utilizes Materialize, Custom CSS, Javascript/JQuery, MongoDB, Node.js, Express, Cheerio.

  Deployed site: <a href="https://infinite-bastion-71270.herokuapp.com/">https://infinite-bastion-71270.herokuapp.com/</a> | GitHub Repo: <a href="https://github.cpm/DoleTM/Web-Scrape">https://github.cpm/DoleTM/Web-Scrape</a>

#### **EXPERIENCE**

## **Orlando Health**, Orlando, FL — *IT Field Support Analyst* | Dec 2019 - Present

- Redesigned internal web page with added buttons for functionality and efficient layout of content.
- Selected out of 50 employees to be responsible for the transfer of all IT related assets of an acquired site.
- □ Provide hardware support to internal and external users of all Microsoft core products including Windows 7 & 10, Active Directory, Outlook, O365 and SharePoint.
- Setup, configure and provision technical office equipment such as Workstations, Laptops, Tablets, Printers and other peripherals.

# **AdventHealth,** Orlando, FL — IT Field Support Technician | Jan 2019 - Nov 2019

- Responsible for configuring and maintaining the physical hardware in 200+ automated supply rooms across 8 hospitals in the Orlando area.
- Analyze trends through client side programs to correct issues by using my database knowledge to prevent problems from occurring in real time.
- Implemented a Kanban board to maintain the flow of project completion and daily activities.
- ☐ Provide technical training to the support staff that utilizes the automated hardware daily.

#### **Injector Support & Service,** Winter Garden, FL — Shipping Manager | Feb 2016 - Dec 2018

- Organized a new 10,000 sqft. warehouse facility, containing 3000+ parts and equipment that maximized efficiency for all departments.
- Recognized by CEO for compiling 8 years of scattered data into one streamlined log within a month.
- ☐ Created a comprehensive procedure handbook that establishes guidelines, sets the daily goals and sustains my organizational knowledge.
- ☐ Improved the return rate of core exchanges by 50% within a year by maintaining a client relationship through weekly phone calls and emails.

### **EDUCATION**

**Full-Stack Web Development Certificate (Coding Bootcamp): University of Central Florida,** Orlando, FL A 24-week intensive program focused on technical programming skills in HTML5, CSS3, Javascript, JQuery, Bootstrap, Firebase, Node Js, MySQL, MongoDB, PHP, AJAX, JSON, Express, Handlebars.js & ReactJS.